edurite.com 2003-04-02

# Edurite Technologies :: Privacy Policy

Given the increasing use of the Internet and the reliance on this electronic world for everything from communications to shopping, controlling and protecting individual information has become a paramount concern.   
At edurite.com, protecting our customers' privacy is something we take very seriously. We endeavor to guard our customers' privacy to the greatest extent possible. 

We also enforce the following privacy policy: 

**edurite.com** collects only information necessary to better serve our customers. We collect the following information through our online registration process: 

  * Email address
  * Password
  * First name
  * Last name
  * Address, city, state, Pincode and country
  * Date Of Birth
  * Do You own a Computer
  * Source for hearing about edurite

edurite.com tracks IP addresses for our customers' protection, giving us the ability to track the exact source of any message in the case of an illegal use of our service. 

edurite.com is committed to data security To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. 

edurite.com is committed to children's privacy, protecting the privacy of the young is especially important to us. For that reason we do not structure any part of our consumer services to attract anyone under the age of 13.  
We require anyone under the age of 13 to obtain their parent's or legal guardian's consent before allowing them to register for an edurite account. We expect that there will be future developments in the area of children's privacy with respect to Internet services that are directed at or may be used by children. We are monitoring these changes and will modify our Privacy Policy as necessary to comply with any new regulations.

edurite.com **** ensures customers' can update their information.  
Our edurite customers can access and modify their personally identifiable information online by clicking on 'My Profile' in the 'My Page' section of edurite.

edurite.com is here to help you.  
Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please call us at 91-80-6722882 or send us an email at [ info@edurite.com.](mailto:info@edurite.com.)
